Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
Sheldon, did you just figure out
a method for synthesizing
a new stable super-heavy element?
Did I?
Well, that can't be right.
No one's ever done that before.
Except me because I just did it!
I Sheldon and his brain, yeah I
I Sheldon and his brain, yeah! I
I've made a horrible mistake.
(Howard:)What are you talking about?
This table,
it's in square centimeters.
I read it as square meters.
(Leonard:)You know what that means?
That Americans can't handle
the metric system?
Amy, I was off by a factor of 10,000.
But the Chinese team
found the element.
Yeah, well, they shouldn't have.
My calculations were wrong.
The greatest scientific
achievement of my life
is based on a blunder.
I'm not a genius.
I'm a fraud.
You know, Sheldon, in neuroscience,
we're forever finding something
in one part of the brain
that we thought was
some-place else.
(Sheldon:)Oh, great,
now I'm worse than a fraud.
I'm practically a biologist.